Let's go full throttle.
So fun.
You are so fun.
More! Let's do more of this!
I have never had so much fun!
What is that guise of yours?
Hurry up and transform.
I want to continue this.
Crap!
Takakura already went full throttle once
so he can't transform anymore!
It's not over yet.
Nobody intervene, please!
Grandma! We gotta help Okarun--
Is that all right?
If we intervene, that means
we're going to exorcise Evil Eye.
Whatcha gonna do?
Want Seiko and the others to help out?
Your knees are shaking.
It's all you can do to stay standing.
Hurry up. I hate having to wait!
Hurry up and transform and fight me!
No way. I don't want to bully weaklings.
Huh?
You can't beat me.
I was convinced from our fight just now.
So I'm not fighting you anymore.
How dare you! Who are you calling weak?
I! Am! Strong!
- Weak.
- Strong.
Strong!
Weak, so weak.
I wouldn't mind taking you on
if you became stronger.
What? I will become even stronger!
But I don't wanna go at it
against someone who'd fight others.
If you're gonna fight,
I want you to only fight me.
Yup, yup.
Fine! I will fight only you!
But you said you were going
to kill all humans, so I can't trust you.
I said, I am only going to fight you!
But I'm busy with school.
I wouldn't mind fighting every so often.
No way! I want to fight
every second of every day!
Then, once a week.
If you can't accept
these conditions, I won't do it.
- This is unfair! You are unfair!
- Master, that's...
This is great.
Sheesh, you turds are a handful.
Turbo Granny, what's going on?
What were you scheming with Okarun?
He started saying some troublesome crap.
Said he wants to be Evil Eye's playmate.
When I previously fought Evil Eye,
he said he wanted
to take playing seriously.
I don't know the reason,
but for Evil Eye, murdering
is the same thing as playing around.
You said so yourself, Turbo Granny,
that Evil Eye is just like a newborn baby.
If that's true, then he just wants
to have fun playing around.
If I can overwhelm Evil Eye,
his attention will be concentrated on me.
Then he won't harm Miss Ayase
and the others anymore.
If I can become stronger, then I might
be able to become friends with Evil Eye.
Then...
Outside of fighting me,
you won't kill any people.
We'll have one fight
every Tuesday after school.
Does this sound good?
Hold on a second!
These guys want to kill off all humans,
so they're saying
they can't agree to that promise.
Until I butcher you, hold on to this.
All right. We'll keep it stored safely.
I want to kill you as soon as I can.
So fun!
Okarun, I...
You didn't hurt anyone.
From now on, nobody will get hurt anymore.
You'll return to a normal life.
Okarun.
Nice weenie!
Why is everyone so put off?
I will take responsibility and store
this cursed item at my shrine.
Be careful.
If anything happens,
contact me right away.
Understood.
We'll visit again someday.
Next time, make sure
you have a tsuchinoko in the shrine.
I can't promise you that,
but I'll be a sleeping bag BooTuber!
Sounds good.
See you.
See ya, Manjiro!
Don't let the curse cause an accident!
Ms. Ayase!
Thank you for all the trouble
that you've gone through!
Jiji's mom.
I'm afraid I can't say my care
was entirely the best. I apologize.
Oh no.
She's being polite!
She's acting properly.
Hey, why're you being so bashful?
Stop that.
Jiji, continue your training
to unleash your chi.
The curse still remains.
If something happens,
make sure to visit us right away.
Okay!
Everyone, I'm sorry
to have caused so much trouble!
I will never forget your kindness!
Pay us back.
Don't worry about it. See ya tomorrow.
Thank you so much!
Man, I'm tired.
Takakura, we should head home, too.
Okarun and Aira, thank you!
No, thank you for housing us for so long.
M-Miss Ayase, I'll see you tomorrow.
- Is that all?
- Huh?
Um, was there anything else?
Is that all?
Jab, jab.
Huh?
What are you doing to Takakura?
Shut up, ugly skank! You hurry on home!
What was that? You swine!
Miss Shiratori, let's go home!
Damn you! Never come back here!
As if I would, you swine!
Oh boy. That was so scary,
wasn't it, Takakura?
Oh man, it's all quiet here now.
So this is what it feels like
when your mind goes blank.
I guess we'll head to the super bathhouse.
Hurray!
What about me?
We're all going.
Hurray!
KAMIGOE STATION
NATURAL HOT SPRINGS
Thank you very much!
Man, it's cold.
We warmed up only to get cold again.
What are we gonna do about the house?
We gotta rebuild it. No other choice.
We have the money?
Nope. That super bathhouse
was our last banquet.
You're joking!
We can go to hell now for all I care.
I just started my part-time job,
so I don't have any money.
Who asked you for money?
I'm not relying on your part-time wages.
So pompous!
You're always acting tough.
Everyone was sleeping over,
so why didn't you
collect expenses for their stay?
Like I need any of that.
Don't act tough.
Don't overexert yourself, okay?
Don't underestimate your Granny.
But what should I do
about my The Idiot Shogun DVDs?
I lost all of my Mr. Ken stuff, too!
What the hell are you, punk?
You're on private property!
Where are you from, moron?
Miss Ayase, hold on a second!
Hey! You're all back.
I got worried about your house,
so Miss Shiratori and I
visited Mr. Mantis on the way home.
We asked him if he could help out
with rebuilding the house.
And he introduced us
to his friend Mr. Ludris.
No way! I'm so sorry!
He's saying it was an honor to be kicked
by a beautiful lady, deez.
No, he's pissed.
He is a construction specialist, deez.
Leave it to him, and the rebuilding
will be done in a jiffy, deez.
I'm sorry, but he's been
looking pissed the whole time.
You're usually really busy.
Go home and play with your kid.
I've always wanted to repay
my gratitude to you, Lady Seiko, deez!
I've only been causing trouble myself,
so I want to do something for you.
You too.
You're barely standing up
so don't wander around so much.
Hurry on back home.
But you're also in a tough spot
right now, right?
- I'm not.
- We very much are.
If you insist on helping out,
then do as you like.
I'm sorry, but can I ask you to?
- Of course, deez!
- Yes!
He's still pissed?
Ta-la-la, ta-dah!
Here.
We'll use this nanoskin for construction.
It's easy to use.
Place the nanoskin somewhere,
and shape it like a clay figure.
And you can make anything you like, deez.
You can make anything, deez.
What? Wicked! Let me make something, too!
What the hell is this?
The nanoskin is made up of
ultra-high-density nanomachines, deez.
What is this? It feels crunchy!
By the way, it's a shape-memory alloy.
Even if it breaks,
the nanoskin will restore itself
to its original form.
Have a solid image in your head
of what you want to make, deez.
The nanomachine will catch
the electric signals from your brain,
and form the shape
exactly like you imagine it.
I see. This is great.
Thanks, Kappa. You saved my ass.
It was nothing, deez.
I'll do anything for Lady Seiko, deez!
Mr. Ludris is also saying it was an honor
to be able to assist a beauty.
You don't understand
what he's saying, do you?
Thank you, Okarun.
You too, Aira.
Man, I'm sleepy. Let's hurry on home.
I'm glad your home is all fixed up.
It kinda felt like my own home,
so it made me uneasy
when it wasn't all right.
Indeed.
It became a hangout for all sorts
of people before I knew it.
We gotta protect it.
Come by again anytime!
Okay!
Thanks, everyone! Come by again!
I totally love all you guys!
You guys are lifesavers!
We gotta pay this favor back.
But for today,
I won't be able to make lunch.
It's fine. Sleep in.
Jin! You're slow! Bang! Bang!
Mom! It's dangerous if you poke
your head out the window!
More like, let me hop on!
Dear, try to keep it down.
Okay, we're here!
All right, Honey, let's do this!
Dear, please be quiet.
Good morning!
The entire Enjoji household
has come to rebuild the house!
Dear, please keep it down.
Huh? It's not broken anywhere.
Oh, Momo!
Grandma's asleep.
I'm sorry for all kinds of reasons.
Don't worry about it.
More like, how's Evil Eye doing?
Actually, about that...
I've turned into Evil Eye a few times.
Oh, Evil Eye didn't do anything.
He's really keeping that promise!
For real?
I don't know
if it's because of the training,
but I feel a connection
with Evil Eye lately.
His excited emotions
get transmitted to me or something.
It's not just hatred. I think he's
enjoying this a surprising amount.
I see.
Well, if something happens, come visit us.
Hey, Momo.
Are you in love with anyone?
Hold up, you look way too disturbed!
Nuh-uh! Not at all!
Your words didn't affect me at all!
H-Hold up! You're badmouthing me now!
Oh! Enjoji!
It's been a while!
You've been absent from school
for some time. What happened?
I was staying home with hopes
of making my cuties all antsy!
What's up with that?
Go get 'em, you flashy guy.
Enjoji, this is the new Pompy flavor!
Wanna try?
Hold on a sec!
You're wearing clothes?
Where is this place?
What'd you think of the taiyaki flavor?
I'll butcher you. This is all too tasty.
Come on, Jiji. That joke
is totally not popular right now.
Oh, it's you. Do you want to be butchered?
I said it's not popular!
Your timing is terrible right now,
so can you go back to Jiji?
No way. This is incredibly tasty.
What, Momo? You being lovey-dovey
this early in the morning?
As if!
That's mine!
What is?
Hey, it's Jiji!
You finally decided to join
the soccer team?
Amazing!
Get back here!
I told you to stop!
WARM
SOLD OUT
Damn it, all the hot stuff is sold out.
Hurry up and give me
that tasty drink from earlier.
I thought I'd let him drink something warm
and get him back to normal.
I have no choice.
At least, it doesn't seem like
he'll attack people.
I guess I'll just see how things go.
What are you writing?
All those I want to butcher!
Whoa! Quiet!
Hey, Enjoji!
Who do you want to butcher
in the middle of class?
All humans!
He's kinda hooked on this one joke.
I told you that's not popular, you turd!
SOLD OUT
What? You're kidding me!
The hot food is all sold out?
I'm sorry,
I'm sold out of most things today.
Wait!
Tasty.
Here, use chopsticks.
Baby steps, I guess.
Hey, did something happen to Jiji?
Like what?
Was he the type to say butcher and stuff?
Maybe he had a change of character.
I know! Maybe the ghost from
the housing complex is possessing him!
- What now?
- Maybe he has a golden ball on him!
Wait, what? How do you know
about the golden ball?
Oh, right. You don't have
a smartphone right now.
It's a hot topic in the group right now.
The ghost in the housing complex.
I see you. I see you, my enemy.
I'm talking to you.
What?!
Momo, is something on your mind?
Leave it to me!
Next episode, "The Secret Art of Being
Attractive." C'mon baby!
Man, my head hurts.
Here's some painkillers!
It tastes like takoyaki!
I wanna ice this guy's head.
Miss Ayase! Please take these instead!
- Thanks.
- I made them with nanoskin!
Like I'd want to take anything like that!